<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>security on pool.malpertus.com</title>
    <link>https://pool.malpertus.com/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in security on pool.malpertus.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons BY 4.0 license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 09:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pool.malpertus.com/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Choose Safer Ports for your Ada Pool</title>
      <link>https://pool.malpertus.com/howto/choose-safer-ports-for-your-ada-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pool.malpertus.com/howto/choose-safer-ports-for-your-ada-pool/</guid>
      <description>Once you decided you want to become an ADA (Cardano) Pool Operator, one of the first technical decisions you have to make is which ports to use for your ADA core node and relay.
Your relay will connect to other Cardano relays and must accept incoming connections from them. Your core node will only connect to your realy and will only accept incoming connections from your relays. Installation guides often propose to use TCP ports 3000, 3001, 6000 or 6001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate Secure and Future-Proof SSH Keys</title>
      <link>https://pool.malpertus.com/howto/generate-secure-and-future-proof-ssh-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 06:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pool.malpertus.com/howto/generate-secure-and-future-proof-ssh-keys/</guid>
      <description>As a Cardano Stake Pool Operator (SPO) you are responsible for the health and security of the Cardano network. As a first step, access to your node or relay must be protected with at least two factor authentication (2FA), based on something you know (like a passphrase) and something you have (like a certificate on your laptop).
The most common tool used to remotely administer a Linux server is SSH. It is by default installed on Linux workstations or servers, and recent versions of Windows 10 include it as an optional component.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
